divshare.com 2019-08-01

# DivShare - Web Site Privacy Statement

This document was last updated on December 8, 2006.

**Acknowledgement and Acceptance of Terms** ****

**Diversion Web Publishing, LLC** ("Diversion Web Publishing" or "DivShare") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our web site.  By accessing www.divshare.com, you acknowledge and fully understand Diversion Web Publishing's Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Web site Privacy Statement.

**Third-party Advertisers and External Links** ****

Related services and offerings with links from this web site, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective web site. Online merchants and others who participate in DivShare services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy.  However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites.  We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

**Information We Collect and How We Use It** ****

DivShare collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our web server logs, the user, and with cookies.

**a. Web Server Logs**

When you visit our web site, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include: 

  * Your Internet protocol address. 
  * The kind of browser or computer you use. 
  * Number of links you click within the site. 
  * State or country from which you accessed the site. 
  * Date and time of your visit. 
  * Name of your Internet service provider. 
  * Web page you linked to our site from. 
  * Pages you viewed on the site.

**b. Use of Cookies**

DivShare may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience.  A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server.  Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.  Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time.  For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.  Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

DivShare reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our web site unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into DivShare.com a site that relies on third-party cookies).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.  Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings, please be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our web site.

**c. Personal Information Users**

Visitors to our web site can register to personalize our service.  When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, e-mail address, and other relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

  * To fulfill your service requests for services.
  * To protect ourselves from liability,
  * To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
  * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

**Use of Web Beacons or GIF files**

Web pages on DivShare.com may contain electronic images known as web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel GIFs – that allow DivShare to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. DivShare prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

**Data and File Security**

DivShare takes all reasonable physical, technical, and managerial steps to safeguard the files and personal information on DivShare.com.  All files are hosted on closely monitored servers in the United States.  However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If DivShare learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. DivShare may post a notice on DivShare.com if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. 

**Accessing Web Account Information** ****

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current.  You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant – [support@divshare.com](mailto:support@divshare.com).

**Children's Privacy**

DivShare is not intended for children under the age of 13.  DivShare does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age.  If DivShare learns of personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on DivShare.com without verified parental consent, then DivShare will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

**Changes to this Statement** ****

DivShare has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement.  When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page.  We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.  Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**Contacting Us**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at [support@divshare.com](mailto:support@divshare.com) or send your comments to:

Diversion Web Publishing, LLC  
Attn: DivShare Privacy  
P.O. Box 605  
Manlius, NY 13104 ****

DivShare will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
